zeegames.com 2018-10-18

# Privacy Policy - Zee Games-Girl Games and Baby Games

Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy**

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which ZeeGames collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a "User") of the http://ZeeGames.com website ("Site"). This privacy policy applies to the Site and all products and services offered by ZeeGames.

**Personal identification information**

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, subscribe to the newsletter, respond to a survey, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, email address. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personally identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities.

ZeeGames.com does not target its Website or services to under 13 year olds, but does take measures to help protect those that happen to be under 13.We take measures to help children protect their privacy while being online. For example, We do not ask children to disclose more personal information than is necessary for them to participate in a particular activity. We do not disclose personally identifiable information of users under 13 years of age to third parties. 

**Non-personal identification information**

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

**Parents and Children**

Are you younger than 13? If so, you should ask your parents for permission for entering your personal information. Are you the father, mother or legal representative of a child playing games on our site and do you wish to withdraw your permission? You can do so at any time. Below a description of how it works is given. In order to cancel an account / a profile the Parent should have access to the email address associated with the account to be deleted. Upon request, the Parent will receive an email message from ZeeGames.com sent to the Parent's email address (that email address should not be the email address of the account to be deleted!) containing a link to our Website. By clicking on the link a specially designed page on ZeeGames.com is opened. On this page a number of data of the Parent and of the profile to be removed are displayed. Here, the Parent should fill in additional information, such as a name, address and telephone number. When the data are sent, an email message will be sent to the email address associated with the account / profile to be deleted. The Parent will have to open this email message containing a link to disable/remove the account. 

**Cookies**

ZeeGames.com uses cookies. A cookie is a simple small file that is sent along with pages of this Website and that is stored by your browser on your computer's hard disk. It is possible to disable cookies, but we advise against this strongly. For turning off the cookies will limit the functionality of the Website considerably. After logging in with your Username and password ZeeGames.com will automatically place a cookie on your computer in order to be able to recognize you during the remainder of a session. The information that is obtained by us in this way will be used by us to remember your games page and to optimize our Website according to your wishes and preferences. Cookies make the website much easier, faster and more personal.You can opt out of some third-party vendor's use of cookies for interest-based advertising by visiting aboutads.info. There are different types of cookies.   

**Necessary**

These cookies are enabled to view ZeeGames.com and to use the basic functions, like the automatic login. 

**Functional**

These cookies make it possible for you to save your preferred setting, like your favorite color and your avatar. 

**Presentation**

Because of these cookies we can show you which games are played most often and which games are best rated. These cookies also make it possible to show the error messages. 

**Third-party**

Because of these cookies we can display advertisements tuned to your interests. 

**Manage cookies**

If you want to delete cookies, you should do this in the settings of your browser. 

**How we use collected information**

ZeeGames may collect and use Users personal information for the following purposes:

\- To improve customer service  
Information you provide helps us respond to your customer service requests and support needs more efficiently.  
\- To personalize user experience  
We may use information in the aggregate to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.  
\- To improve our Site  
We may use feedback you provide to improve our products and services.  
\- To run a promotion, contest, survey or other Site feature  
To send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.  
\- To send periodic emails  
If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, they may do so by contacting us via our Site.

**How we protect your information**

We adopt appropriate data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures to protect against unauthorized access, alteration, disclosure or destruction of your personal information, username, password, transaction information and data stored on our Site.

**Sharing your personal information**

We do not sell, trade, or rent Users personal identification information to others. We may share generic aggregated demographic information not linked to any personal identification information regarding visitors and users with our business partners, trusted affiliates and advertisers for the purposes outlined above.

**Third party websites**

Users may find advertising or other content on our Site that link to the sites and services of our partners, suppliers, advertisers, sponsors, licensors and other third parties. We do not control the content or links that appear on these sites and are not responsible for the practices employed by websites linked to or from our Site. In addition, these sites or services, including their content and links, may be constantly changing. These sites and services may have their own privacy policies and customer service policies. Browsing and interaction on any other website, including websites which have a link to our Site, is subject to that website's own terms and policies.

**Advertising**

Ads appearing on our site may be delivered to Users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile non personal identification information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This privacy policy does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

**Ads by Google**

Our website contains advertisements that are supplied by the U.S. company Google. Use may be made of cookies and other technologies, such as Google Analytics, to track how Users use the Website. The information thus obtained, including the address of your computer (IP address), will be transmitted to, and stored by, Google on servers in the United States.   
Google uses this information to track how our Website is used, to report to us about the Website and to be able to offer its advertisers information about the effectiveness of their campaigns. Google may make available this information to third parties if Google is legally required to do so, or in as far as such third parties process the information on Google's behalf. This is beyond our control. 

**Google Adsense**

Some of the ads may be served by Google. Google's use of the DoubleClick cookie enables it to serve ads to Users based on their visit to our Site and other sites on the Internet. DoubleClick uses "non personally identifiable information" and does NOT track personal information about you, such as your name, email address, physical address, etc. You may opt out of the use of the DoubleClick cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html "Google ad and content network privacy policy")

**Changes to this privacy policy**

ZeeGames has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will post a notification on the main page of our Site, revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

**Your acceptance of these terms**

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy and terms of service. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

**Contacting us**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at:  
ZeeGames  
http://ZeeGames.com

 **This document was last updated on 20.08.2013**
